<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Karan Shah</title>
    <link>http://www.karan.sh/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Karan Shah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.karan.sh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>http://www.karan.sh/project/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.karan.sh/project/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Bayesian Model for Cosmic Shear</title>
      <link>http://www.karan.sh/research/livermore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.karan.sh/research/livermore/</guid>
      <description>Still under construction
Introduction The gravitational lensing of distant galaxies by mass along the line-of-sight is a sensitive probe of both the expansion and structure growth rates of the Universe. The massive amount of data from the Large Synoptic Survey Telescope (LSST) and other surveys can be used to infer the properties of cosmic shear. We describe how Hierarchical Bayesian Models can be used to infer these properties while marginalizing nuisance parameters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>http://www.karan.sh/project/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.karan.sh/project/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Hugo</title>
      <link>http://www.karan.sh/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.karan.sh/about/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a static site engine written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 Cobra Viper J Walter Weatherman Cast  Learn more and contribute on GitHub.
Setup Some fun facts about Hugo:
 Built in Go Loosely inspired by Jekyll Primarily developed by spf13 on the train while commuting to and from Manhattan. Coded in Vim using spf13-vim  Have questions or suggestions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>http://www.karan.sh/project/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.karan.sh/project/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>http://www.karan.sh/project/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.karan.sh/project/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.karan.sh/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.karan.sh/contact/</guid>
      <description> Still under construction
Contact details </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>http://www.karan.sh/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.karan.sh/cv/</guid>
      <description>Still under construction
In case the embedded version appears funky, open PDF in a new tab: PDF Link
This browser does not support PDFs. Please download the PDF to view it: Download PDF.
 
Open in a new tab: PDF Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>http://www.karan.sh/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.karan.sh/education/</guid>
      <description> Still under construction
Georgia Institute of Technology Atlanta, GA
BS in Physics BS in Computer Science (Intelligence and Modeling-Simulation Threads)
Thesis: Title: “Analysis of Uncertainty in Machine Learned Density Functionals”
Advisor: Dr. Andrew Medford
Expected: May 2018 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>